$HealthOptions	Health Options
$MagickaOptions	Magicka Options
$StaminaOptions	Stamina Options
$EffectIntensity	Effect Intensity
$EffectType	Effect Type
$HealthIntensity_Desc	Intensity of the low health screen effect.
$HealthPercentage_Desc	Percentage at which the low health effect starts.
$MagickaIntensity_Desc	Intensity of the low magicka screen effect.
$MagickaPercentage_Desc	Percentage at which the low magicka effect starts.
$StaminaIntensity_Desc	Intensity of the low stamina screen effect.
$StaminaPercentage_Desc	Percentage at which the low stamina effect starts.
$HealthEffect_Desc	Screen effect when low on health. Some effects may not stack with others. Multiple effects of the same type will cause flickering.
$MagickaEffect_Desc	Screen effect when low on magicka. Some effects may not stack with others. Multiple effects of the same type will cause flickering.
$StaminaEffect_Desc	Screen effect when low on stamina. Some effects may not stack with others. Multiple effects of the same type will cause flickering.
$ResetSettings	Reset All Options
$ResetSettings_Desc	Reset all settings to their defaults and remove current effects. You will lose your settings!
$ResetSettings_Confirm	You are about to reset all settings to their defaults. Are you sure?
$LockApply	Applying Effects...
$LockReset	Resetting Settings...
$ResetSettings_ConfirmDesc	Settings will reset after window is closed.
